# Igor Augusto Brandão

Capitão Mor Gouveia Av, Lagoa Nova, Natal-BR.

igorabrandao@gmail.com / +55 84 99943-1545

Zip Code: 59076-400

# **Objective**

Enroll in a Computational Biology and Bioinformatics doctoral program, besides through the acquired knowledge/experience create biotechnology business and solutions to bring technological innovation to our country, create jobs and improve people's lives with the developed products.

## **Education**

## Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte (2019-2020)

Master's degree, Bioinformatics and Computational Biology

Project: Systems biology approaches in the investigation of articulation points in KEGG pathways

Website: https://igorabrandao.com.br/kegg-pathway-bottleneck/banner.pdf

## Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte (2017-2018)

Specialization degree, Residency in Information Technology applied to the Legal Area.

## Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte (2014-2018)

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology: Software Engineering.

#### Presbyterian University Mackenzie (2010 - 2013)

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management: Finance.

#### Fatec Carapicuíba – Technology College (2010 - 2012)

Technical license, Systems Analysis: Web development.

# Work Experience

#### Freelancer in software development (2012-2018)

Self-employed.

#### Residency in Information Technology applied to the Legal Area (2017-2018)

Rio Grande do Norte Court of Justice.

#### Full Stack Developer (2017-2017)

Interativa Digital.

#### Equity researcher (2013-2013)

CFA Institute.

#### Software Developer (2009-2009)

Kuadrus Informática.

## **Intern Software Developer (2008-2009)**

Visual Mix.

## **Publications**

#### The Role of Vitamin D and Sunlight Incidence in Cancer (2019)

Journal: Anti-Cancer Agents in Medicinal Chemistry.

The relationship between vitamin D deficiency and oxidative stress can be independent of age and gender (2019)

Journal: International Journal for Vitamin and Nutrition Research.

Study of the relationship between vitamin D deficiency, sunlight incidence and skeletal/extra skeletal diseases (2019)

Journal: International Journal for Vitamin and Nutrition Research.

#### **Technical Skills**

- R and Python programming;
- Relational databases and NoSQL;
- Data Mining;
- C, C++, Java, Dot .Net programming;
- Web development with PHP, Yii, RESTful API (backend);
- Html 5, Css 3, Javascript, Jquery (front-end);
- AngularJS, 2/4/5/6/7 (front-end framework);
- Ionic (mobile);
- Wordpress (CMS);
- Software architecture and requirements specification;
- Docker and virtualization (vagrant);
- Linux, Windows and Mac OS.

### **Awards**

#### 2nd Place at Flourish Hackathon (2019)

Sebrae of Rio Grande do Norte.

#### Winner at Microsoft Hackathon (2015)

Federal Institute of Rio Grande do Norte.

#### Best relational database project at Microsoft Student to Business (2010)

Microsoft Innovation Center.

### **Other Informations**

Linkedin:

http://www.linkedin.com/in/igorbrandao

Personal website:

https://igorabrandao.com.br